弄好可以也烫下我的制服吗
Hey, will you steam my uniform next?
哟  真有意思
Yeah, w... interesting.
你还记得我们这段对话吗
Do you recall this conversation?
"莱纳德  要不要跟我摊挂烫机的钱"
"Leonard, want to go halfsies on a steamer?"
"不要  谢尔顿  我们又用不到"
"No, Sheldon, we don't need a steamer."
看来有人现在自食恶果了吧
Looks like that rumpled chicken's come home to roost.
这是你要的化妆海绵
Here are the make-up sponges you asked for.
谢啦  我本来以为我还有不少
Oh, thanks, I thought I had more.
靠  你的化妆品比我还多
Damn, you've got more makeup than I do.
而且还比我用的都高级
You've got better makeup than I do.
这个老娘借了
Yeah, I'm borrowing this.
这是我动漫大会专用化妆品
This is my Comic-Con makeup.
我爱你  但有些东西是男子汉们
I love you, but there are some things
不能与女友分享的
a man doesn't share with his girlfriend.
十分明智的原则
That's a wise policy.
我曾为化装比赛借用了我妹妹的化妆品
I once borrowed my sister's makeup for a costume contest.
结果被传染到红眼病
Got a terrible case of pinkeye.
幸好那年我刚好是想化装成僵尸
Yeah, but luckily, I was going as a zombie.
因此还赢得了第二名呢
I won second place.
你们不是才去过动漫大会吗
I feel like you guys just went to Comic-Con.
上次是圣地亚哥动漫大会
That was San Diego Comic-Con.
这次是贝克尔斯菲动漫大会
This is Bakersfield Comic-Con.
这次的有比较好吗
Is that better?
其实规模小了很多
Well, it's a lot smaller.
但重心主要放在漫画书上
It's more about the comic books.
以前传统的大会都是这样
The way these conventions used to be
而不是像现在的好莱坞电影潮
before they went all Hollywood.
简单扼要地回答你  这场没比较好
So to answer your question, no, it's not better.
那你们干嘛还去啊
Well, then why are you going?
始终还是漫画大会
It's a comic book convention.
就如同披萨或粒子加速器一样嘛
You know, it's like pizza or particle accelerators,
就算做得不好  也还是可以接受
even the stinky one's still pretty good.
好吧
All right.
那祝你们玩得开心
Well, you guys have fun.
那估计是周日晚再见了吧
I guess I'll see you Sunday night.
-是的  行
- Yeah. - Okay.
你等一下
Oh, hang on a second.
举着这个
Hold this.
这是干嘛
What was that for?
作为别人不信我有美女女友时的证据
To show people when they don't believe me.
生活大爆炸
第六季  第十三集
这样最爽了
Oh, this is the best.
如果你平日吃早餐时配酒喝
You have booze with breakfast on a Tuesday,
人家会说你酗酒
you got a problem.
但如果是周末这样  就能推说是早午餐
You do it on the weekend, you got brunch.
谢尔顿不爱早午餐这套
Sheldon doesn't believe in brunch.
他无法忍受吃饭时
He can't stand being at a table
一边有人在吃早餐煎蛋卷
where one person's having an omelet
而另一边有人在吃午餐三明治
and another person's having a sandwich.
他真是不厌其"烦"啊
He's not exhausting at all.
莱纳德发的短信  说他们在路上了
It's Leonard, he says they're on the road
正"曲速前进"贝克尔斯菲市呢
and headed for Bakersfield at "warp speed."
可能这含羞草鸡尾酒上头
Maybe it's the Mimosa,
但我就大发慈悲给他回个"哈哈哈"吧
but I'm gonna give the kid an LOL.
他们兴奋这些事的样子真可爱
It's cute how excited they are.
你们应该看看霍华德
You should have seen Howard
为了参加大会  缝了整周服装的样子
sewing his costume all week for the convention.
霍华德什么时候学的缝纫啊
When did Howard learn to sew?
他小时候  每隔几个月
When he was a little boy, every couple months,
都要帮他妈把旧裤子重新缝大一点
he would have to let his mom's pants out.
我真不知道他们为什么会去这些大会
I don't even understand why they go to these conventions.
对啊
I know.
他们四个都在知名大学工作
The four of them work at a major university.
他们都超级聪明
They're all super smart.
怎么会还在痴迷12岁小孩的玩意呢
How can they still be into something made for 12-year-olds?
我是不介意啦
I don't mind it.
我觉得霍华德只是内心有孩子气的一面
I think Howie's just in touch with his inner child.
不过有时候他穿着蝙蝠侠睡衣上床时
Although when he comes to bed in his Batman pajamas,
我都感觉是其实他就是个小孩
sometimes it feels like I'm touching his inner child.
可能是因为他们从小被欺负到大吧
It's probably because they were bullied growing up.
在一个人自身无力反抗时
In a world where you can't fight back,
超级英雄能满足他们心中的愿望
superheroes provide meaningful wish-fulfillment.
现在我对自己欺负过的那些人感到内疚
Now I feel bad for picking on all those kids.
但我也要替自己辩驳
Although, in my defense,
当年丹尼·比佛要不想被欺负得满嘴泥
if Danny Biffle didn't want to eat a mouthful of dirt,
就不该戴着一个欠扁的蠢领结来上学
he shouldn't have shown up to school wearing a bow tie.
我没有看过漫画书呢  你们呢
I've never even read a comic book. You guys?
-没  -没有过
- Uh-uh. - No.
这东西对他们生命那么重要
I mean, it's such an important part of their lives.
我们也许该去试着看看啊
Maybe we should try reading some.
你说真的吗
Seriously?
漫画店离这里也不远啊
The comic book store isn't far from here.
这主意太棒了
That is an amazing idea.
靠  我是喝了多少杯啦
Okay, how many of these have I had?
我觉得你该开卫星导航器
I think you should turn on the GPS.
开了啊
It is on.
可你没开语音导航功能
But the turn-by-turn voice option isn't on.
你要是打开那个
I know I'd feel more safe
我会感觉到加倍安心呢
if you turn on the turn-by-turn voice option.
我爱死语音导航功能了
I love the turn-by-turn voice option.
真的只开了10英里而已吗
Has it really only been ten miles?
为了让你闭嘴  我现在就开
I'm turning it on, but just to shut you up.
莱纳德  向左转
Leonard, bear left
沿着210洲际公路继续前行
and continue on Interstate 210.
语音导航的那人听起来很懂行啊
Ooh, sounds like that fellow knows what he's talking about.
我要是你  一定会洗耳恭听的
I'd put on my listening ears if I were you.
你对导航器干嘛了
What did you do?
我网上找到了个破解软件
I found a hack online.
能让我把自己录制的声音档
I was able to upload MP3 recordings
上传到你的导航器
of my voice to your GPS.
这太酷了
That is so cool.
反对  一点都不酷
Counterpoint, no, it's not.
继续沿着210洲际公路
Continue on Interstate 210
前行5英里
for five miles.
以下是一则关于洲际公路的有趣小知识
Here's an interesting fact about interstates.
你不是吧
Really?
别吵  人家说是有趣小知识呢
Shh, he said it's interesting.
洲际公路数字命名的规则是
Interstates are numbered as follows.
偶数公路走东西向
Even-numbered routes run east and west,
奇数公路走南北向
odd-numbered routes run north and south.
三位数公路表示环绕郊区
Three-digit route numbers indicate bypasses
或支路
or spurs.
瞧  莱纳德  那有座桥
Look, Leonard, there's a bridge.
冲出去死了算了
Drive off it.
我们离华斯克巨岩公园不远了
You know, we're not that far from Vazquez Rocks.
《星际迷航》有很多集都是在那里拍的
Oh, they shot a lot of Star Trek episodes out there.
我们的化装服就在车里
We've got our costumes in the trunk.
我们可以去那里  拍几张照片
We could go there and have a little photo shoot.
好主意
Great idea.
我两周没碰过碳水化合物了
I haven't had a carbohydrate in two weeks.
瘦得颧骨都凸起来了  不赶紧拍照
These cheekbones need to be in front of a camera
不然一块椒盐卷饼下肚  就打回原形了
before I eat a pretzel and they're gone.
好啊  听起来不错
Yeah, that sounds fun.
好极了
Oh, smashing.
-莱纳德  那你知道怎么去吗  -不知道
- Now, Leonard, do you know how to get there? - No.
幸好车上有人知道
Yeah, well luckily, someone in the car does.
重新计算路程
Recalculating.
在等待的同时
While we're waiting,
你知道是哪一任总统将
do you know which president signed
《洲际公路系统法案》签署成为法律吗
the Intestate Highway System Act into law?
答案将在14英里后公布
The answer, coming up in 14 miles.
你们肯定都猜不出来
None of you will get it.
是艾森豪威尔[美国第三十四任总统]
It's Eisenhower.
他们干嘛盯着我们看
Why are they staring?
哪要理由
Who cares?
好好享受就行了
Just soak it in.
你们好呀
Hello, boys.
拜托不要盯着看  不过是女生而已
Could you please stop staring? They're just girls.
你们又不是没在电影或漫画里见过
It's nothing you haven't seen in movies or in drawings.
斯尔图特
Hey, Stuart.
什么风把你们吹来了
Wh-What brings you guys here?
我们想听听你对漫画书的建议
We were looking for a recommendation about comic books.
我的建议是  千万不要以卖漫画书为生
Oh, well, I recommend you don't open a store and sell them.
不是啦  我们只是好奇
No, we were just wondering
为什么男生这么喜欢看漫画
why the guys like this stuff so much,
所以我们想试试看
so we thought we'd give it a try.
好的  你们觉得自己可能会喜欢什么类型
Oh, okay. What do you think you might be into?
超级英雄漫画  奇幻漫画  漫画小说  日本漫画
Superhero, fantasy, graphic novels, manga--
再盯人家我就拿水管喷死你们
I swear I will turn a hose on you.
那咱家几个都喜欢什么类型的漫画
What kind of comics do the guys like?
什么类型都会看一点
Um, a little bit of everything.
大部分是超级英雄系列的
Mostly superhero stuff.
好吧  那谁是最厉害的超级英雄
All right, well, who's the best superhero?
你不能在这里问这种问题
You can't ask a question like that in here.
你是想挑起宅男骂战吗
Are you trying to start a rumble?
那你推荐什么
Well, what do you recommend?
我想想
Well, uh, let's see.
有阳光帅气的基本款英雄
You've got your basic clean-cut good guys--
《超人》  《蜘蛛侠》  《美国队长》
Superman, Spider-Man, Captain America.
有黑暗系的另类英雄
Then you have your darker anti-heroes--
《蝙蝠侠》  《金刚狼》  《惩罚者》
your Batman, your Wolverine, Punisher.
哇  我还就喜欢坏小子
Ooh, I do love a bad boy.
你那怕仓鼠的男友  就是最好的"证明"啊
As evidenced by your boyfriend and his fear of hamsters.
如果我是你  我会选《成人童话》第一集
If I were you, I'd go for Fables number one.
画风复杂精致
The artwork is sophisticated,
情节千回百转
it's intelligently written,
而且没有物化或有女性刻板印象
and it doesn't objectify or stereotype women.
哇  《雷神》
Ooh, Thor!
他真性感
He's hot.
对啊  的确是
Yeah, he kind of is.
再上点粉
And we're blending,
and we're blending,
大功告成
and we're done.
我知道数据机器人不应该笑
I know Mr. Data isn't supposed to smile,
但我要笑一个
but here it comes.
来吧  伙计们  开拍啦
Come on, guys. Let's do this.
快点  我出汗出得秃头套都要掉了
Yeah, I'm sweating my bald cap off.
我们第一个造型要摆什么
So what's our first pose going to be?
先摆一个《星际迷航》的经典打斗场面吧
I say we begin with a classic Star Trek fight scene.
我去设定时
I'll set the timer.
谢尔顿  你这算哪门子的打斗姿势
Sheldon, how is that a fight pose?
数据机器人的武器就是脑子
Mr. Data's weapon is his mind.
我正挥舞它呢
I'm wielding it.
相位枪对准博格人
Phasers on the Borg!
《霹雳娇娃》姿势
Charlie's Angels.
好的  下一个是什么
Okay, what's next?
我们拍几辑性感魅力的照片
Now let's do some sexy glamour shots.
我来挑动气氛
I'll set the mood.
好  这张好
Yeah, nice one.
就这样
That's right.
天啊
Oh, my God.
莱纳德  有人在偷你的车
Leonard, someone's stealing your car!
什么  喂  喂
What? Hey, hey!
回来  别走
Come back here! Stop!
偷车是犯法的
Stealing is against the law!
真不敢相信
I don't believe this.
混蛋
Son of a bitch.
我打电话报警
I'll call 911.
糟糕
Wha...
不是吧  我的手机在其他裤子里
Oh, no, my phone is in my other pants.
-我的也是  -我也是
- Oh, so is mine. - Mine, too.
有人有办法吗
Anybody got any ideas?
没有
Nope.
唯一能做的事就是怪罪某人
The only thing left to do now is assign blame.
都怪你
Nice going.
谁会在光天化日之下公然偷走别人的车啊
What kind of a person steals another person's car in broad daylight?
谁会把车钥匙留在车里不拿走啊
What kind of person leaves his keys in the car?
不是说好都怪库萨帕里了吗
I thought we agreed this was all Koothrappali's fault.
你说得对
You're right.
都怪你
Nice going.
有车
Car.
这些人怎么搞的  干嘛不停车
What is wrong with people? Why don't they stop?
也许这样更好
Maybe we're better off.
万一我们上了神经病的车就惨了
You know, what if we were to get in a car with a crazy person?
照照镜子吧  谢尔顿
Look at us, Sheldon.
我们就是神经病
We're the crazy people.
也许我们该举个牌子
Well, perhaps we should hold up a sign
告诉来往车辆我们的精神很正常
that assures passing motorists of our mental competence.
这主意真棒  那你还不赶紧做牌子
Good idea. Why don't you get started on that?
算了  咱们用走的吧
Come on, let's just start walking.
这附近肯定有加油站之类的
There's got to be a gas station or something nearby.
就因为你穿着船长的制服
What, you think just because you're wearing a captain's uniform,
你就能发号施令了是吗
you're in charge?
是的
Yes.
好吧
All right.
我看完了
Hmm, okay, I'm done.
你们怎么看得那么快
How did you guys finish so fast?
大部分都只是图片啊
I don't know, there were a lot of pictures,
有一页上甚至只写了一句"受死吧"
and one page only had the word "Brakkadoom!"
行  聪明人脑子快  可我有街头智慧
Yeah, well, I have street smarts.
你们怎么看
So, what'd you guys think?
书里有许多打斗场景
Well, there was a lot of action,
情节跌宕起伏
and the story moved along at a brisk pace.
总体来说
It was, overall...
我该怎么形容呢
what's the word I'm looking for?
-蠢  -超蠢的
- Stupid? - So stupid.
真不知道莱纳德怎么会对这玩意这么着迷
I don't know how Leonard can get so caught up in this.
太荒唐了  他们竟然花大量的时间
It's crazy; they spend hours
讨论这些虚无缥缈的东西
arguing about things that don't even exist.
-真是浪费光阴  -可不是嘛
- What a waste of time. - I know.
什么一把重到只有雷神才举得起的铁锤啊
A hammer so heavy that no one else can pick it up?
我觉得不是因为它重
I don't think it's heavy.
而是铁锤上有某种魔法
I think it's some sort of magic,
所以只有雷神才能举起它
so only Thor can lift it.
这更说不通啊
That makes even less sense, I mean...
不不  就应该是这样
No, no, no, it doesn't.
雷神是神
Thor is a god.
铁锤是他的  只有他能用
The hammer is his; only he can use it.
就像谢尔顿和他的牙刷
It's like Sheldon and his toothbrush.
或者谢尔顿和他那两片诱人薄唇
Or his thin, beckoning lips.
等一下
Okay, hang on,
要是雷神正拿着铁锤呢
what if Thor's hand is on the hammer?
如果他正拿着铁锤发力
I mean, if he's touching it with his god magic,
那是不是我也可以拿起它
does that mean I could lift it?
-不是  -是的
- No. - Yes.
到底怎样
Well, which is it?
我们是不是漏了什么细节
Maybe we missed something.
再看一遍吧
Let's read it again.
-好吧  -行
- Okay. - Yeah.
想喝点茶吗
You want some tea?
好主意  我帮你
Good idea. I'll help you.
不是要一起再看一遍吗
Wait, I thought we were reading.
要的
We are.
你先开始吧  我们晚点不要紧
We're just, uh, giving you a head start.
真希望我妈妈在这儿
I wish my mom was here.
我们就都可以在她的影子下乘凉了
We could all hang out in her shadow.
漫漫沙漠行  毛裤贴我身
Wool pants in the desert.
熊熊烈日下  蛋蛋火上蒸
I feel like I've got poached testicles.
可怜的你啊
Oh, you poor thing;
瞧你那汗流的
you're sweating.
可真是比车被人偷了还可怜
That's so much worse than having your car stolen.
保险公司会赔你辆新车
Insurance is gonna buy you a new car.
请问谁能赔我大雕
It's not gonna de-funk my junk.
先生们
Gentlemen,
不要再满腹牢骚了
a little less bellyaching.
我们是星际舰队的军官
We're Starfleet officers
是博格集合体的一份子
and a member of the Borg Collective.
谢尔顿  拜托  我现在真没心情入戏
Please, Sheldon, I am so not in the mood.
莱纳德
Leonard,
我们一直都在梦想
all our lives we have dreamed
进入我们所挚爱的幻想世界
of finding ourselves inside one of the fantasy worlds we love.
看看现在的我们
And look at us.
现在我们真正成为了
At this moment, we are, in fact,
星际迷航的先遣登陆队
a Star Trek landing party
被困于荒芜凋敝的陌生环境
stranded in an alien and unforgiving environment,
只能依靠自己的智慧  坚毅
relying only on our wits, our fortitude
和勇气
and our moxie.
只要我们有这些品质
As long as we have those things,
-没有什么可以阻止  -书呆子
- nothing can stop... - Nerds!
我恨死这星球了
I hate this planet.
看  铁锤上写着呢
It says right here on the hammer,
"只要是配得上的人手持铁锤
"Whoever holds this hammer, if he be worthy,
均可获得雷神的神力"
shall possess the power of Thor."
等一下  谁能决定他是否配得上
Hold on, who decides who's worthy?
是铁锤决定吗
Does the hammer decide?
-是的  -不是
- Yes! - No!
它无法决定
It can't decide.
它只是个铁锤
It's a hammer.
是你说它有魔力的
You said it's a magic hammer.
对  但它不能做决定啊
Yeah, it can't make decisions.
哈利·波特的魔杖都能选主人
If Harry Potter's wand can make decisions,
雷神的铁锤凭什么不行
why can't Thor's hammer?
你要是非要拿魔杖和铁锤比
Okay, if you're going to start comparing wands and hammers,
那我没啥话好对你说了
I can't even take you seriously.
你好
Hello.
请倒四杯水
Uh, four glasses of water, please.
你们要什么吗
Anything for you guys?
能借电话用一下吗  我们的车被偷了
Can I use your phone? Our car got stolen.
你们怎么不叫史考特传送你们上舰啊
Why don't you ask Scotty to beam you up?
史考特是第一代系列人物
Scotty was on the original series,
而我们是《下一代》的
and we're Next Generation.
所以...
So...
糗的是你们
joke's on you.
我们跟他不是一起的
We're not with him.
你不能在外太空拿起任何东西
You can't pick something up in outer space.
-在太空里根本就没有"起"的概念  -是吗
- In space, there is no up. - Oh, yeah?
那为什么每天太阳都会升"起"呢
Then how does the sun come "Up" every day?
很难反驳如此的街头"智慧"啊
Hard to argue with those kind of street smarts.
莱纳德和谢尔顿有成箱的漫画书在对面屋
Leonard and Sheldon have boxes of comics across the hall.
我们为何不过去找找答案
Why don't we go look at those?
很好  这样你们就会发现
Oh, great! Yes! And then you will see.
我没错  因为如果我们在外太空
I am not wrong, because if we were in outer space,
任何人都有可能举起锤子
then anyone could pick up the hammer
因为在失重环境下  它是漂浮在空中的
because it would be floating around in a weightless environment.
没错  看书慢的人也懂科学
Yeah, that's right, the slow reader used science.
去死吧
Suck on that.
车里有什么值钱的东西
Was there anything valuable in the car?
衣服  钱包  手机
Our clothes, our wallets, phones.
还有价值三百美元的化妆品
And about $300 worth of makeup,
所以现在偷车贼可以化妆成任何样子
so this thief could look like anyone right now.
化妆品
Makeup?
不奇怪
Sure.
我们本打算去贝克尔斯菲的动漫大会
Uh, we're going to the Comic-Con in Bakersfield.
那里有个大型的化装比赛
They have a big costume contest.
其实没听起来那么蠢啦
It's cooler than it sounds.
还好  听起来还挺酷啊
I don't know, sounds pretty cool.
本来就很酷
I-It is.
那里不仅只有漫画书
It's not just comic books.
还有人偶  玩具
They've got action figures, toys,
还有"电子世界争霸战"主题舞会
a Tron-themed dance party...
行了  他已经了解有多酷了
Okay, he gets how cool it is.
我要问的都问完了
I think I have all I need here.
需要我帮你们联络谁吗
You guys need me to call someone?
我猜应该是你们妈妈吧
I'm guessing your moms?
多谢  我们自己能搞定
Thanks, but we've got it covered.
好了  我刚跟我妈通完电话
Okay, I just talked to my mom.
她帮我们租了辆车
She arranged for us to get a rental car.
太好了
Great.
我们还可以去动漫大会
We can still make it to Comic-Con.
你开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
遭了这么多罪  我现在只想回家
After all we've been through, I just want to go home.
别这样嘛
Don't be like that.
拜托  霍华德  劝劝他
Come on, Howard, talk to him.
我支持莱纳德
I'm with Leonard.
我受够了
I'm done.
好吧  那看来是二对二了
Fine, then I guess it's two against two.
怎么决定
How do we decide?
事实上  是三对一
Actually, it's three against one.
什么
What?!
那任务怎么办
What about the mission?
是你说我们是现实中的先遣登陆队
You said we were a real-life landing party.
我们不是
Yeah, well, we're not.
我们是幻想的先遣登陆队
We're an imaginary landing party
在现实中被人丢垃圾
who had real-life garbage thrown at us
现实中陌生人认为我们是白痴
by real-life strangers who think we're idiots.
跟你说实话
And to tell you the truth,
我开始觉得自己像白痴了
I'm starting to feel like one.
我现在就想回家
I want to go home now.
好吧
Okay.
那我们好歹从进取公司租车吧
Did we at least rent the car from Enterprise?
懂吗  进取号哟
Get it? Enterprise?
去死吧  明明很好笑
Screw you. That's funny.
那绿巨人在雷神举着锤子时
Well, what if the Hulk picked up Thor
把他连人带锤举起来  那会怎么样
while Thor is holding the hammer?
会怎样
Yeah?
这样根据传递性质
Then by the transitive property of picking things up,
就是绿巨人举起了锤子
Hulk picked up the hammer.
不
No.
是绿巨人举起了雷神  雷神举起了锤子
Hulk picked up Thor, Thor picked up the hammer.
等等
Okay, hang on.
如果我去酒吧勾搭[举起]了一个男的
If I go to a bar and pick up a guy,
他又勾搭了一个女的  然后我们仨一起离开
and he picks up a girl, and then we all leave together,
那那个女的算是我勾搭上的吗
did I pick up the girl?
这是真事吗
Did that ever happen?
喂  是讨论我还是讨论雷神啊
Hey, are we talking about me or are we talking about Thor?
要我说  这是我们最后一次出门
Well, I say that's the last time we ever go outside.
看这里
Look, right here.
红巨人举起了雷神的锤子
Red Hulk is picking up Thor's hammer
因为雷神拿着锤子
'cause Thor's touching it.
不  因为他们在外太空
No, it's because they're in space.
而且他只是碰到了带子
He's really just touching the strap.
带子是锤子的一部分
The strap is part of the hammer!
不是的
No, it's not!
她们是在争论漫画书的内容吗
Are they actually arguing about comic books?
不  这不可能是真的
No, that can't be right.
也许"雷神之锤"
Maybe "Thor's Hammer"
是新的指甲油颜色
is a new color of nail polish.
红巨人肯定是配得上锤子
Then Red Hulk must be worthy.
红巨人怎么配得上啊
How could Red Hulk be worthy?
你又不了解他的生平
You don't know his life!
只有一个合理的解释了
There's only one logical explanation.
在沙漠的某处
Somewhere in the desert
我们穿越到另一个平行空间了
we crossed into an alternate dimension...
在这个空间  我们生活中的女性
where the women in our lives
终于懂得欣赏真正的伟大著作了
can finally appreciate great literature.
如果这是平行空间
If it's an alternate dimension...
听起来先遣登陆队可以执行任务了
sounds like a job for a landing party.
舰长  有何指令
Captain, what are your orders?
我看我们要调查一番
I say we investigate.
等等
Wait.
她们可能有攻击性
They might be hostile.
好吧  不过调成击晕模式
Fine, but set them to stun.
如果把佩妮汽化了
If we vaporize Penny,
我上哪儿再去找这么正点的女朋友呀
I'll never find a girlfriend that pretty again.
有趣的事实
Fun fact:
艾森豪威尔总统是在病房里签署的
President Eisenhower signed the Federal Aid Highway Act
《联邦政府助建公路条例》
from his hospital room.
还真的很有意思啊
Wow, that is interesting.
每天都能学到新知识
You learn something new every day.
那么  你能说出是哪四个州府
Say, can you name the four state capitols
没有通州际公路吗
that are not served by the interstate system?
又来道智力题  爽
Ooh, another quiz. Yes!